# MOTIVATED AND INNOVATIVE AGILE FULLSTACK DEVELOPER AND TESTER WHO'S STRONG WITHIN SPRING BOOT OG .NET

**Laust Eberhardt Bonnesen** 

Click on a text to open its link:

- Nørre boulevard 98, 1 tv. 4600 Køge
  - in laust-eberhardt-bonnesen
- @ laustslaustede@gmail.com Caustrup



## **PROFILE**

**+45 60548098** 

I am a 27-year-old software developer and tester who, in addition of being motivated and innovative, is resourceful, responsible and collaborative with the ability to be self-driven and are experienced in implementing, maintaining, developing, debugging, analysing and designing fullstack code.

These characteristics about me, I find to be important in a work environment, in which code can be written with good elements such as reliability, stability and security, which the product can at the same time be user-friendly with a large selection of functions and the code must also have the possibility to continually be able to be further improved through scalability and readability with plenty of documentation.

## **SKILLS**

Here are the different skills in categories within the different tools and knowledge I possess.

During the other chapters, areas of these skills are further described.

## FRAMEWORKS

Spring Spring Boot | .NET SwelteKit React Maven Vue

React Native Vite Unity

# DATABASE

MySQL MSSQL SQLite

# **PROJECTMANAGING**

ΧP Waterfall ITIL Scrum

Test-driven Event-driven

## **LANGUAGES**

C# **JSON** JavaScript Java

#### **VHDL** TypeScript Verilog

## MARKUP/STYLING

**CSHTML JSP HTML XML** 

**VERSION CONTROL** 

GitLab

CSS

Git

# **TESTING**

Unit Acceptance Integration JUnit **XUnit** Postman AAA

## $\mathbf{UML}$

Class ER **Package** Domain State machine Sequence Use case

GitHub

# CLOUD

CI/CD Azure **AWS** Firebase

## **ARCHITECTURE**

REST API MVC **GRASP SOLID** Hibernate

# CONTAINERS

Docker Kubernetes

# **IDEA**

IntelliJ Rider VS code

## **COURSES AND EVENTS**

- · Prosa Firewall and Filtering
- Prosa Kubernetes Security
- Prosa Secure Coding
- Prosa Introduction to AI and Machine Learning
- Prosa Introduction to Vue.js
- Maersk Observability and Efficiency with Spring Boot 3
- Jetbrain Virtual Threads and Structured Concurrency in Java
- Jetbrain Java OAuth

#### SPEAKING

Danish: Native speaking

English: Fluent Swedish: Familiar German: Familiar Portuguese: Beginner

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Backend Intern | Infomedia

august 2022 - November 2022

🔻 Pilestræde 58, 1112 København



- Used Scrum as agile project managing.
- Worked within:
  - NET Core with C#
    MVC structured APIs
    MSSQL
    Dapper
    Bulkcopy
    MediatR
- Gained experience of working in a workplace together with other both skilled and nice colleagues, but also further evolved my programming skills to a higher level, with a lot of useful feedback from the company.
- Tested and debugged their functions through XUnit with:
  - Unittesting
  - Acceptance tests
  - Integration tests
- Today Infomedia uses the code I have worked with in their production.

#### Course Creator | App Academy

iii June 2022 — August 2022

Sdr Havnegade 7, 6000 Kolding



- Creating and recording a Java Spring / Spring Boot online course with:
  - Presentations.
  - Assignments.
  - Quizzes.
- It has improved my ability to share, be resourceful and formulate knowledge to others on a technical level.
- The course is currently in use by App Academy.

## **EDUCATION**

#### Computer Science | KEA - Copenhagen School of Design and Technology



- September 2020 January 2023
- Guldbergsgade 29E, 2200 København
- Education of code implementation, design patterns, various diagrams and project management, mostly with agile principles such as Scrum and XP.
- Fullstack programming and software development course:
  - Java Spring Boot

- JDBC

JavaScript

- Maven - Hibernate - CSS - JUnit - HTML - MySQL
- Electives courses:
  - ASP.NET MVC with C#
    - \* Identity
    - \* Entity Framework
    - \* CSHTML \* SQLite

- React Native with TypeScript
  - \* Redux
  - \* Firebase
  - \* Store

- IT operations
  - \* Hardware
  - \* ITIL
  - \* Security

- Other courses such as business and technology.
- The focus has been on mixing theory and practical ability.
- An internship is included.
- Most of the education projects have involved collaboration.

### Electrical Engineering | DTU - The Technical University of Denmark

- Anker Engelunds Vej 1, 2800 Kgs. Lyngby



- Two terms of an electrical engineering bachelor.
  - Containing courses of:
    - \* Digital design \* Mathematics
    - \* Electronic circuit

- Included some programming introductions with:
  - \* Java
  - \* C
  - \* VHDL
  - \* Verilog

## **PROJECTS**

#### ASP.NET MVC with C# exam project

February 2022 - June 2022

Link: ( Laustrup/Second

Architecture

\* MVC

\* Pages

- Fullstack Razor project
  - Languages \* C#
    - \* CSHTML
    - \* CSS
- Framework
  - \* ASP.NET Core

  - Razor

  - \* Entity Framework
- Features
  - \* Scaffolding
  - \* Migration
  - \* Identity
  - \* Bootstrap
- Database
  - \* SQLite
  - \* DbContext
  - \* Application
    - File db
- The project was about a webshop, where people can login and upload secondhand products to sell.

#### KEA final exam project

November 2022 - January 2023 - Today

#### Links:

- Compare the com
- Comparison of the property of the property
- Compare the compared to the

- Fullstack with backend in priority and frontend on hold momentarily.
  - Languages:
- Framework:
- Database:
- Architecture:

Comparison of the property of the property

Testing:

- \* Java
- \* Spring Boot
- \* JDBC
- \* REST API
- \* JUnit

- \* JavaScript
- \* Maven
- MySQL
- \* MVC

Postman

- \* HTML/CSS
- \* Lombok
- \* H2

- \* SOLID \* GRASP
- \* AAA
- The program is about giving musicians the possibility to create gigs and promote them.
- Still an ongoing project after the exam.
- Own utilities used and build.
- Test driven.
- Uploaded to Maven.

#### React Native with TypeScript exam project

iii February 2022 - June 2022

Link: \(\bigcap\) Laustrup/ChatroomsApplication

- Frontend project with Firebase as a Realtime Database API.
  - Language\* TypeScript
- Framework

\* Redux

\* React Native

- Features
  - \* Firebase
  - \* Component based
- Architecture
  - \* Store
  - \* Screens
- The project was about a chat room application, where people could log in and create a post.

### CreeThor

iii July 2023 - I dag

#### Links:

- Caustrup/CreeThor
- Game engine project.
- Runs on lwjgl with GLFW and openGL, which are Java Maven dependencies and some C, that are executed on the dependency.
- Graphic logics are working with vertex and fragments in a glsl file.

## **ABOUT ME**

I see myself as a friendly, curious and open person who is social and enjoys everything creative and with logical elements mixed together.

In my spare time I either work on my side projects or spend time on some of my other interests, but can also have a quiet evening to relax.

An important thing for me is to keep evolving and learning new things and concepts that fascinate me.

I believe that life should be fun and exciting, but at the same time I want to have a good influence on others and the generations to come.

# **INTERESTS**

Music Band Philosophy

Beer/wine clubs

Tablefootball/tennis

Billard/pool | Gaming

Board games | History

Politic | Fitness

